In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard. The
market cap of the company is Rs
55823 crore
[music] which
gives 79%
and here you can see the chart of the company. There is a
discount in the valuation of the company at this time and the earnings of the company are increasing, which
means there is a very good opportunity to buy at this time. If we
talk about the positive points in the company, then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the
dividend payout of the company is
24.3% and if we talk about the negative points, then
in the last 3 years the promoter's holding has
reduced by 7 point 84%
and here you can see that the
profit of the company has increased in quarter ton
[music]
48.02489 and the public's holding is 11 points.
Subscribe to Barmer channel.